

# Paola Guerrero

**MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER** 



(+52) 55.1475.0175



paolags@gmail.com



paolags.wixsite.com/book



Niños Héroes 102-406C Delegación Benito Juárez

I maintain a professional approach in the development of specific goals, plans and deadlines to prioritize, organize and carry out my job. I have a very good eye for details and colors. With the experience I have gained in design, web design, multimedia, events, e-learning and digital marketing; I am the integral solution for the needs of your Company.



## Education

# 1994–1998 Escuela Nacional de Artes Plásticas UNAM.

Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Design Professional License: 4599812



# Work Experience

#### 2018- Today Richmond ELT Mexico

Multimedia & E-learning eLearning. Author Avallain platform with HTML5 & CSS3. Design and animation of e-books, flashcards, posters and interactive karaokes for English language teaching books. Management of CMS and AWS platforms.

#### 2020-2021 Virtual Latinos

Digital y Multimedia - Part time Corporate design. Design of digital material for social networks -infographics, videos, animations-. Video edition and animation for tutorials and trainings. Presentations.

### 2006-2017 • Cambridge University Press

#### Design

Design and administration of the website.
Design of minisites, landing pages, newsletter.
Social media ads, graphics and videos.
Promotional videos. Design of posters,
promotional, flyers, banners and printed
advertising in general. PowerPoint templates.
Coordination of events and national tours of
foreign authors to promote our materials.

## 2005 COMA InterActive

Proyect Manager

Design, development and coordination of animation, e-learning and interactive projects.

## 2003-2004 • CACTO, Arte e Ideas

Multimedia & Web Designer
Design and development of web pages,
animations and interactive projects.

#### 2000-2003 ♦ Producció

## Producciones Virtuales/Funktion Technologies

Multimedia Designer

Design and development of web pages, animations and miniseries online.

# Languages

Spanish | First language English | B1 Level French | A2 Level

# Software

#### Web, Multimedia & Graphic Design

Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Premiere Pro, InDesign, Flash/Animate, Acrobat Professional, Dreamweaver, Office, Camtasia Studio, Plataforms: Author Avallain, Trello, AWS, CMS, WordPress, Wix

## Programming languages

HTML5, CSS3

#### Operative System

MacOS, Windows.

# Extra Curricular Education

- ★ Introducción al Desarrollo Web Responsive con HTML y CSS | Domestika
- ★ Creación de una web profesional con WordPress | Domestika
- Layout web con CSS Grid, Flexbox y otras técnicas modernas | Domestika
- ★ CSS Grid: First Look | Lynda.com
- ★ CSS: Animations | Lynda.com
- Gráficos vectoriales SVG: ilustrar y animar con código | Domestika
- ★ Creating a Responsive HTML Email | Lynda.com
- ★ HTML5, CSS3, and jQuery with Adobe Dreamweaver | Learn by Video
- ★ Introducción a la programación en JavaScript | Domestika
- ★ UI & Web Design using Adobe Illustrator CC | Skillshare.com
- ★ Diseño UX: experiencia de usuario UX / UI + Figma | Udemy
- ★ De la animación al código | Vénturus
- ⋆ Diseño de páginas web | FOLDER X
- \* Adobe Illustrator CC Advanced Training | Skillshare.com
- ★ Introducción a After Effects | Domestika
- ★ Adobe After Effects CC Animated Infographic Video & Data Visualisation | Skillshare.com
- ★ Diseño de contenido gráfico para redes sociales | Domestika
- ★ Introducción al community management | Domestika
- Creación y edición de contenido para Instagram Stories | Domestika